searcheurope.com 2014-02-09

# Search Europe - privacy policy

**Privacy Statement for Search Europe** SearchEurope.com, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Search Europe.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

Our site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, or age). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

This site contains links to other sites. **SearchEurope.com, Inc.** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, or age). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

Our online surveys ask visitors for demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code or age). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies.

 **Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. **Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. **Supplementation Information**  
This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. **Children's Guidelines**  
This site does not collect online contact information from children without prior parental consent or parental notification. 

This site does not collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent. The TRUSTe Children's Guidelines are being met by this site.

 **Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [contact_us@searcheurope.com](mailto:contact_us@searcheurope.com?subject=Re%20Search%20Europe)  

 **Correct/Update**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email: [contact_us@searcheurope.com](mailto:contact_us@searcheurope.com?subject=Re%20Search%20Europe)  

 **Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact SearchEurope.com, Inc. 5756 Descartes Circle Boynton Beach, FL 33472, USA [contact_us@searcheurope.com](mailto:contact_us@searcheurope.com?subject=Re%20Search%20Europe)
